Nfon Andrew

Bamenda, Cameroon



nfonandrew73@gmail.com



+237681610898



linkedin.com/in/nfon-andrew-7703a11a0



https://andrew21-mch.github.io

Summary

Been Full Stack Developer with PHP/Laravel/Blade, Javascript for 3years, Certified on Coursera as System Administrator and looking for roles in this field to gain experience.

Excellent at communication and community management

Currently learning Java/Springboot, Javascript/Vuejs, Python/Django and updating my knowlege on php/laravel

Experience

zuri. Software Developer

Zuri Team, Inc.

Aug 2022 - Present (3 months +)

PHP/Laravel Developer

💟 Software Developer Intern

Nasia Tech. LLC

Feb 2022 - Aug 2022 (7 months)

Full stack Trainee

Java/Springboot, HTML/CSS/Javascript

Full-stack Developer

Skye8

Jan 2020 - Present (2 years 10 months +)

Serving startup as Full stack developer with PHP/Laravel HTML/CSS/Javascript

zuri. Peer Mentor

Zuri Team, Inc.

May 2022 - Aug 2022 (4 months)

Partime Tutor and Mentor At Zuri Training In Partner with Ingressive for Good

GNOME Ambassador

GNOME Foundation

Jul 2021 - Mar 2022 (9 months)

OpenSource awareness and gnome technologies

Intern

HNG Internship

Aug 2021 - Oct 2021 (3 months)

Education

alx_africa

2019 - 2023

Certificate, Computer Software Engineering Jun 2021 - Mar 2023

National higher polytechnic institute

Bachelor of Engineering, Computer Engineering

Licenses & Certifications

- (A) JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures freeCodeCamp
- Spring boot Essential Training LinkedIn AemQja4XKBJdjv4Z0vqes9kAPt-x
- in Spring: Framework in Depth LinkedIn
- in Creating Your First Spring Boot Microservice LinkedIn

Skills

Project Management • Teamwork • Laravel • Back-End Web Development • programmer • PHP • JavaScript • HTML/CSS • Python • Java